altafsir.com 2019-07-01

# Altafsir.com Privacy Policy - إخلاء مسؤولية

**Altafsir.com Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
This website is owned by the  Royal Aal al-Bayt Institute for Islamic Thought and operated by the Integrated Technology Group (collectively the "Altafsir Team"). Before you commence using this site (the "Site") please go over the privacy policy below.   
  
**1.** **Information Collection and Use**

The Altafsir Team will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Altafsir Team collects information from our users at several different points on our website. No individual information about any visitor will be released to any third party without that visitor’s permission. The information collected will be used in the aggregate only and is for the sole internal use of the Altafsir Team.   
  
**2\. Registration**

In order to use some features of our website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration the user is required to give his/her contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender).  
  
**3\. Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
  
**4\. Logs**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track the user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  

**5\. Sharing**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  
  
**6\. Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that the Altafsir Team is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.  
  
**7\. Referrals**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. The Altafsir Team will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. The Altafsir Team stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact the Altafsir Team at [altafsir@itgsolutions.com](mailto:altafsir@itgsolutions.com) to request the removal of this information from our database.  
  
**8\. Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.

All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to [altafsir@itgsolutions.com](mailto:altafsir@itgsolutions.com) .   
  
**9\. Special Offers**

We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and unsubscribe option below.  
  
**10\. Changing/Updating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by e-mailing our customer support at [altafsir@itgsolutions.com](mailto:altafsir@itgsolutions.com) .  
  
**11\. Subscribe/Unsubscribe**

Our users are given the opportunity to unsubscribe at any time from receiving any e-mail from us. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the e-mail or e-mail us at [altafsir@itgsolutions.com](mailto:altafsir@itgsolutions.com) .

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.  
  
**12\. Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

Home
